<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on Faisal Kholid | Site &amp; Portofolio</title>
    <link>http://faisalkholid.github.io/posts/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on Faisal Kholid | Site &amp; Portofolio</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 07 Jan 2020 15:03:00 +0800</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://faisalkholid.github.io/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Creating a New Theme</title>
      <link>http://faisalkholid.github.io/2014/creating-a-new-theme/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 28 Sep 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://faisalkholid.github.io/2014/creating-a-new-theme/</guid>
      <description>Introduction This tutorial will show you how to create a simple theme in Hugo. I assume that you are familiar with HTML, the bash command line, and that you are comfortable using Markdown to format content. I&#39;ll explain how Hugo uses templates and how you can organize your templates to create a theme. I won&#39;t cover using CSS to style your theme.
We&#39;ll start with creating a new site with a very basic template.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Migrate to Hugo from Jekyll</title>
      <link>http://faisalkholid.github.io/2014/migrate-from-jekyll/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 10 Mar 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://faisalkholid.github.io/2014/migrate-from-jekyll/</guid>
      <description>Move static content to static Jekyll has a rule that any directory not starting with _ will be copied as-is to the _site output. Hugo keeps all static content under static. You should therefore move it all there. With Jekyll, something that looked like
▾ &amp;lt;root&amp;gt;/ ▾ images/ logo.png  should become
▾ &amp;lt;root&amp;gt;/ ▾ static/ ▾ images/ logo.png  Additionally, you&#39;ll want any files that should reside at the root (such as CNAME) to be moved to static.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>UI Incoming Call</title>
      <link>http://faisalkholid.github.io/2020/uicall/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Jan 2020 15:03:00 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://faisalkholid.github.io/2020/uicall/</guid>
      <description>UI Incoming Call Tools : adobe XD Icon : Material Icon</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>UI Login</title>
      <link>http://faisalkholid.github.io/2019/uilogin/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Dec 2019 16:26:14 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://faisalkholid.github.io/2019/uilogin/</guid>
      <description>UI Login For Community Website Tools : Figma Icon : Material Icon</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>UI Notification</title>
      <link>http://faisalkholid.github.io/2019/uinotification/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Dec 2019 13:29:35 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://faisalkholid.github.io/2019/uinotification/</guid>
      <description>Notification UI/UX Tools : Adobe XD, Icon : Material,&amp;hellip; a simple UI notification.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>UI Music Player Portofolio</title>
      <link>http://faisalkholid.github.io/2019/uiportofolio/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Dec 2019 13:13:12 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://faisalkholid.github.io/2019/uiportofolio/</guid>
      <description>Music Player Music Player UI A simple UI made with Adobe XD and Material Icon.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Puisi Malam</title>
      <link>http://faisalkholid.github.io/2019/puisi/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Dec 2019 14:13:56 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://faisalkholid.github.io/2019/puisi/</guid>
      <description>BARU KEMARIN Baru kemarin aku coba mencintai seseorang, memikirkannya setiap malam, stalking dia tiap jam, sampai tak bisa aku terpejam, anganku terlalu jauh kepadanya, hayalku terlalu tinggi kepadanya.
Kulitmu yang putih mata yang bulat yang setiap aku pandang terasa nyaman dan sejuk, kau membawa perindu dalam matamu sehingga aku tak kuasa mengedipkan mataku sendiri.
Namun, malam ini disaat hari bahagiamu datang nama yang kamu tag di storymu menyadarkan bahwa aku hanya angin lalu dalam hidupmu, namun aku turut bahagia atas harimu itu.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>(Hu)go Template Primer</title>
      <link>http://faisalkholid.github.io/2014/goisforlovers/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Apr 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://faisalkholid.github.io/2014/goisforlovers/</guid>
      <description>Hugo uses the excellent Go html/template library for its template engine. It is an extremely lightweight engine that provides a very small amount of logic. In our experience that it is just the right amount of logic to be able to create a good static website. If you have used other template systems from different languages or frameworks you will find a lot of similarities in Go templates.
This document is a brief primer on using Go templates.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Getting Started with Hugo</title>
      <link>http://faisalkholid.github.io/2014/hugoisforlovers/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Apr 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://faisalkholid.github.io/2014/hugoisforlovers/</guid>
      <description>Step 1. Install Hugo Go to Hugo releases and download the appropriate version for your OS and architecture.
Save it somewhere specific as we will be using it in the next step.
More complete instructions are available at Install Hugo
Step 2. Build the Docs Hugo has its own example site which happens to also be the documentation site you are reading right now.
Follow the following steps:
 Clone the Hugo repository Go into the repo Run hugo in server mode and build the docs Open your browser to http://localhost:1313  Corresponding pseudo commands:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Introduction aux modèles (Hu)go</title>
      <link>http://faisalkholid.github.io/2014/goisforlovers.fr/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Apr 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://faisalkholid.github.io/2014/goisforlovers.fr/</guid>
      <description>Hugo utilise l&#39;excellente librairie go html/template pour son moteur de modèles. c&#39;est un moteur extrêmement léger qui offre un très petit nombre de fonctions logiques. À notre expérience, c&#39;est juste ce qu&#39;il faut pour créer un bon site web statique. Si vous avez déjà utilisé d&#39;autre moteurs de modèles pour différents langages ou frameworks, vous allez retrouver beaucoup de similitudes avec les modèles go.
Ce document est une introduction sur l&#39;utilisation de Go templates.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>